

Yuji Mori Full Stack Developer | Web3 |



Morioka, Iwate, Japan

Yuji is a full-stack engineer with over 8 years of experience in web development, managing all aspects of the development process. He's worked on 50+ projects and solved complex business problems in various industries including marketing, healthcare, eCommerce, real estate, and car insurance. Yuji has consistently saved costs while increasing profits. He's ready for an opportunity to use his skills to grow your revenue exponentially.

Work Experience

React | Angular | Go

Web3 Developer | Dapp Specialist • Sophophilia Studios





- -Implement Metamask/Web3 functionality into a primary web application
- -Developed the back-end of a web service using Express framework in addition to the front-end with JavaScript
- -Develop deployment scripts for HardHat using Javascript

View project

Senior React Developer • Neighborhoods.com LLC

November 2019 - October 2020

- -Worked on a real-estate website with React, Redux, SCSS, Webpack.
- -Interpreted the Invision design into a mobile-first responsive front-end UI.
- -Redesigned the websites from scratch using create-react-app and custom Webpack configuration.
- -Optimized React UI with lazy-loading and modern browser APIs.
- -Delivered new features and the storybook build a component optimization.

View project

Senior Web Engineer • Yuzu Solutions LLC

September 2018 - June 2019

- -Served as a lead developer for building an educational marketing simulation app using Django, React, Redux.
- -Worked in a SCRUM team.
- -Collaborated with data scientists and back-end developers to determine the best UI/UX.
- -Re-skinned the app with a new theme and design.
- -Implemented an Excel-like form with excellent UX.

View project

Full stack Web Engineer • Scoutible







- -Worked on building a game-based platform to assess a candidate's soft skills and increase the odds of a successful hire.
- -Improved outdated APIs written in Python.
- -Improved Python codebase design by adding reusable base classes based on design pattern.
- -Improved code design using React.js and Redux-saga standard practice.
- -Managed deployment process using GAE.
- -Improved storing app state info in local storage to use redux store.

View project

Software Developer • Self-employed

May 2016 - October 2017

- -Developed websites and mobile applications for over 50 clients.
- -Helped multiple clients finalize problematic projects by providing the needed expertise to bring projects to release.
- -Created a white-labeled iOS application to support a large number of online forums.
- -Built mission-critical applications that scale and support thousands of users.
- -Integrated social media tools and SDKs into various websites and mobile applications.

View project

Software Engineer • Tokyo Electric PowerCompany

August 2015 - March 2016

- -Acted as a front-end and a back-end engineer (full-stack)
- -Oversaw the MVP and beta launch

View project

Education



Faculty of Science and Engineering, Iwate University

Bachelor of Programming

Skills

- Web Development
- Mobile Application Development
- Chat solution
- Blockchain Development

Languages

- English Professional
- Japanese Native or Bilingual



2010 - 2014